https://www.swing-trade-stocks.com/privacy-policy.html

Start here
Beginners:
Learn The Basics
Intermediate:
The Strategy
Advanced
Reviews
Q&A
Click to subscribe »
Spotlight:
Get your free expertly-researched stock pick delivered to your inbox »
Privacy Policy and Disclaimer
Thank you for visiting swing-trade-stocks. com (the "Web Site") and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Web Site unless you choose to provide that information. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Web Site.
What Type of Information We Collect
The server on which the Web Site is located collects and saves only the default information customarily logged by web server software. Such information may include the date and time of your visit, the originating IP address, and the pages and images requested.
Third parties may be placing and reading "cookies" on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on this website.
"Cookies" are data sent to your web browser from a web server (such as Google) that can uniquely identify your computer and store information about user preferences. Most web browsers will accept cookies by default, but they can be set to reject cookies, either from all websites or from specific sites. You can also manually delete cookies from your web browser. These options are generally set through a "Privacy" setting in your browser setup.
Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Copyright
The materials found on the Web Site are protected by United States and other copyright laws, except for works of the United States Government pursuant to 1 U.S.C. Section 105. The selection, arrangement and presentation of all materials (including information in the public domain), and the overall design of the Web Site are copyright © August 3, 2005, Swing-Trade-Stocks.Com . Permission is granted to view and print materials from swing-trade-stocks.com for the non-commercial purpose of viewing, reading and retaining for reference. Any other copying, distribution, retransmission or modification of information or materials on this site, whether in electronic or hard copy form, without the express prior written permission of Swing-Trade-Stocks.Com , is strictly prohibited.
No Warranties
Swing-Trade-Stocks.Com DOES NOT MAKE ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR ENDORSEMENTS WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE) WITH REGARD TO THE WEB SITE, THE MATERIALS, ANY PRODUCTS, INFORMATION OR SERVICE PROVIDED THROUGH THE WEB SITE, OR ANY SITES LISTED THEREIN, AND THE WEB SITE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY COST OR DAMAGE ARISING EITHER DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY FROM ANY SUCH TRANSACTION. THE WEB SITE DOES NOT WARRANT THAT IT WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE OR THAT DEFECTS IN IT WILL BE CORRECTED. THE WEB SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS, AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. IN NO EVENT WILL THE WEB SITE OR ITS MEMBERS, MANAGERS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS AND THE ASSIGNS OF SAME BE LIABLE FOR (1) ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR INFORMATION, AND THE LIKE) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEB SITE, THE MATERIALS OR ANY INFORMATION, OR TRANSACTIONS PROVIDED ON THE WEB SITE OR DOWNLOADED FROM THE WEB SITE, EVEN IF THE WEB SITE OR ITS AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, OR (2) ANY CLAIM ATTRIBUTABLE TO ERRORS, OMISSIONS OR OTHER INACCURACIES IN THE WEB SITE, THE MATERIALS AND/OR LISTINGS OR INFORMATION DOWNLOADED THROUGH THE WEB SITE. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, THE WEB SITE'S LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless the Web Site and its members, managers, officers, employees, agents and the assigns of same, from and against any and all loss, costs, expenses (including reasonable attorneys' fees and expenses), claims, damages and liabilities related to or associated with your use of the Web Site and any violation of this Privacy Policy by you.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
This Privacy Policy constitutes a contract made under and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Florida
Compensation
The website owner may receive compensation for the endorsement of some products on this website.
The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made on this website. The website owner will only endorse products or services that are believed, based on the expertise of the owner, to be worthy of such an endorsement.
Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.
All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network or through affiliate programs.
Last Update
This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 30, 2011.
Contact Information
Questions or comments regarding the Web Site should be submitted here.
Learn to trade
Trading Course
This is a home study course that teaches you how to trade stocks from full-time swing trader Kevin Brown. Definitely one of the best swing trading eBooks that you can buy.
Read my review »
Featured Article
How to Scan For Stocks
Looking for the best stocks to trade?
Here is a list of the best scanning and charting services available today.
Stock scans »
Swing Trading System
Trade Triangles
Are you looking for an easy trading system to follow that takes all the guesswork out of when to buy and sell stocks?
Check out my review of MarketClub here »
Advertisements
Stock Market Software
Tradespoon
Click a button and this software program will tell you what the stock price will be into the future. Give this service a test drive. I think you will really enjoy tinkering around with this trading algorithm!
Read review of Tradespoon »
Downloads
Free Technical Analysis eBooks
Download 14 free technical analysis and stock market related eBooks - at no charge!
Download »
Recommended Reading
What Are the Best Stock Market Books?
See my list of the top technical analysis books that I think every trader should own.
Best stock market books »
Beginners: Learn the Basics
Learn The Basics of Swing Trading »
How to Use Stage Analysis »
Why You Should Trade Trending Stocks »
How to Use Elliott Wave Analysis »
How to Use Moving Averages »
How to Draw Trend Lines on a Stock Chart »
Intermediate: Trading Strategy
Learn a Simple Swing Trading Strategy »
Trading Strategy Overview
»
Learn About the Traders Action Zone »
How to Trade Pullbacks »
Entries and Exits For Swing Traders »
Learn This Market Timing Strategy »
Advanced: Swing Trading Tactics
Learn Some Advanced Swing Trading Tactics »
How to Scan For Stocks »
Learn How to Short Stocks »
4 Chart Patterns For Swing Traders »
How to Use Fibonacci Retracements »
5 Example Trades For Swing Traders »
